In the Clou 2025.2 version, the version generator has added pants and a group of products.
Now, except for T-shirts, you can use the existing size data or AI generation data to quickly and conveniently create a more diversified clothing version.
We will take you through two cases separately.
First, let's take a look at how to create a version by directly inputting the measured value of the chair.
When you use the version generator to create a version, the system will automatically place and sew according to the existing virtual model.
So we first need to open the virtual model.
Next, find the version generator in the main menu bar 2D and click open.
After clicking on the bottom of the pull menu, you can see that pants and a group of products have been added.
For the pants product, we have provided gold waist pants and leisure pants, two preset styles.
For a group of products,
we have provided a round skirt and an A skirt as preset styles.
Next, let's choose pants and leisure pants together.
Directly input the size of the control part to create a version.
We will switch to the simple mode for initial value adjustment.
The control part contained in the simple mode will be displayed at the bottom.
If here, the top pull menu is switched to the regular mode,
you can input and modify more detailed parameters.
Reasonable activation or stop parameters can help you to adjust your version efficiently and freely.
For example, for parameters such as waist and waist activation, you can directly input the value.
The stop parameters will be automatically calculated based on actual data and other input measured values.
First, we will switch to the simple mode to quickly adjust the value.
First, let's look at the saving part.
The version generator will be based on the waist and hip width inserted at the top.
This function can help you to quickly create a saving.
It is very useful.
At present, it only supports the input of the saving number.
Distance and length and other detailed values are in the active state.
The connection icon next to the saving number indicates that these detailed values will be calculated according to the waist and hip width.
Click the connection icon again to activate the specific settings.
You can directly input the value.
We will click the connection icon again.
And from the front pocket section, we will enter the number.
Click the next button.
The number will be adjusted.
Click the save icon at the top.
Close the save function.
Next, let's see the waist and waist options.
If you open the total length icon on the right, you can input the total length of the waist and hip.
After inputting the total length, the length will automatically assign the front and back pieces according to the ratio.
If you need to set the waist and hip of the front and back pieces separately, you can also turn off the total length.
Here I will turn on the total length and input 750mm as the total length.
When entering the value, you need a calculator.
You can click the right button in the input box.
You can open the calculator.
When the calculation is complete, press the OK button.
You can directly apply the value to the input box.
Or you can simply calculate it directly in the input box.
We just opened the total length icon on the right side of the waist and hip.
And set it to 1000mm.
Next, set it to 270mm.
At the same time, open the total length on the right side of the ankle.
And adjust it to 500mm.
You can see that the size of the thigh will automatically increase to match the width of the crotch.
Now we turn to the back crotch part.
I will keep 292.1mm on the spot.
Just change the province from two to one.
Finally, let's come to the waist part.
I will adjust the width value.
Because the waist is 750mm.
I will input 730mm as the waist width.
Slightly reduced to fit the waist.
The height is set to 40mm.
So far, we have set the basic version in the simple mode.
Now, please switch to the regular mode at the top of the menu.
After switching to the regular mode, you can directly modify the thigh.
Or the specific parameters of the province that was not activated before.
The thigh of the back crotch is set to be slightly wider.
About 320mm.
Turn off the connection on the left side of the back crotch province.
We will adjust the length to 130mm.
This set of complete data can be saved by clicking the save button in the upper right corner of the generation board.
Save as csv file.
No need to manually input values again during subsequent operations.
Just click the open button in the upper right corner.
You can add the csv file saved earlier.
When you click open, you can see the spring.
Please note that the current generation board is only supported by the csv file.
After entering all the values, click the create button in the lower right corner.
Then click the left button in the window in 2D.
The creation of the version can be completed.
To verify whether the version is based on virtual models,
Automatic arrangement and completion of sewing.
You can switch to 3D window simulation and check.
You can see that it is based on virtual models.
Automatic arrangement and sewing.
So far, we have mastered the existing model based on the existing model.
Thank you.
In this video, we have learned how to create a version based on existing data.
This is suitable for the size and shape of the target version.
To be clear.
Next, let's use the AI version generator to create a cluster.
In the version generator, click the AI version generator icon in the upper right corner.
The AI version generator window will appear.
You can enter the prompt in the prompt option card.
Or directly in the image option card.
Upload reference pictures to create a version.
In the prompt option card.
I will choose half a group A half a group.
You can use the key word suggestion at the bottom.
Choose A self-improvement version.
You can also manually enter the umbrella group.
After freely setting your key word prompt.
Finally, click start to generate.
After generating the required picture.
Click the start to generate button at the bottom.
Change it to a version.
If you look at the 2D window.
You can find that the control part data has been automatically filled in according to the generated picture.
The current AI generated version is based on the outline of the version.
Therefore, as you can see.
The details such as zipper, door handle, or pocket are not reflected in the paper.
The function is planned to be improved in the future version.
However, you can use the basic version of the AI suggestion.
Then slightly adjust it in the version generator.
Next, let's see the image option card together.
Select the umbrella group.
Original umbrella group.
Then upload a reference picture.
You can see that this umbrella group has been saved.
And there used to be a middle gap in the middle part.
Click start to generate.
After the generation is complete.
Close the AI version generator window.
Check the virtual version form.
You can further adjust the value.
We can adjust the value of the control part according to the effect.
For example, the waist is below 100.
Here I will set the waist as the total length.
And modify its length to 650 mm.
The hip is wide and modified to 900 mm.
The bottom is modified to 870 mm.
Because the model has a middle gap in the front.
So we can change the front and back groups.
All changed to symmetrical.
You can also remove the waist plate according to your own needs.
According to the displayed virtual version.
The adjustment effect has reached the expected.
If you need further detailed adjustment.
You can show all measurements on the right side of the module.
Check the hidden projects such as the middle gap.
And click on the detailed information icon.
Activate these parameters to achieve more precise control.
After adjustment.
I will click the create button to generate the version.
Close the version generator window.
If you simulate in 3D window.
You can find that the version generated by AI and modified by us has been perfectly worn.
The version generator is now expanded to include pants and shorts.
To help you easily and quickly design more diversified fashion styles.
It can be used to enter the existing size.
Accurate creation of the version.
It can also be used to quickly achieve creative visualization using the AI function.
I hope you can actively use these functions in version design.